LUTFIA AISYA

FULL STACK DEVELOPER



Amsterdam West

aisya.lutfia@gmail.com

+31 6 87937940

in @aisyafia 🗗

@aisyafia

PROFILE

I am an adaptable and innovative person with 5+ years experience in research, business strategy and project management. I decided to learn web development because being a female foreigner is tough, especially when searching for proper job in the Netherlands. I wanted to boost my skill to compete in the employment market. I am creative, resilient, smart and I enjoy being a part of international and intergenerational environments.

TECH SKILLS

Git & Github JavaScript HTML/CSS **Typescript** React SASS Redux MUI Axios Next.js Node.js Spring Boot **Express** Bootstrap PostgreSQL Figma Python Sequelize

EDUCATION

MSc in Development Studies University Antwerp, Belgium 2015 - 2017

Bachelor in Banking and Finance Indonesia Banking School, Indonesia 2008 - 2012

TECH JOURNEY

Full-Stack Development | October 2022 - January 2023 | Codaisseur

10 intensive weeks where I learnt and applied modern technologies from back-end to front-end to build full-stack web. Scored 90% in the final assessment. Created the following projects:

FinWise

A full-stack web where users can upload their Dutch-formatted pay slip and receive financial explanation on its components. Involves: React, Redux, React-Pdf, Axios, Sequelize, Express

Front-end [간 Back-end [간

• <u>Hangman: Movie Edition</u> ☐ <u>Repository</u> ☐

A group project, recreated the Hangman game to guess movie titles from the TMDB API

A self-practice project using Typescript, React, Redux and MUI.

• Big Sister for Small Sister ☑ Repository ☑

A page for women volunteer, focusing on supporting young, marginalised girls in North Kenya.

• Cocktailogy [Repository []

A self-practice project using Typescript, Nextjs, and Tailwind.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Front End Web Developer Intern | September 2023 - February 2024 | Amsterdam, NL NLC - The European Healthtech Venture Builder

Designed, created, and styled the front-end part of internal applications. Tech tools: Figma, Spring Boot, HTML/(S)CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Git

Warehouse Supervisor | January - October 2022 | Amsterdam, NL

Gorillas | On-demand grocery delivery service

Key responsibilities: small-scale performance management, administration and customer service. Tech tools: Quinyx, Zenput, Slack, in-house Dashboard

Store Assistant | January - December 2021 **| Amsterdam, NL Bayu Food and Art |** An Indonesian restaurant and art gallery

Key responsibilities: customer service and inventory management

Editor | August - September 2020 | Delft, NL

GIZ Brussels Office | German Social-Development Agency

Freelance editorial work on policy papers. Focus area: climate change and energy policy in Indonesia

Business Development Lead | January 2018 - January 2020 | Jakarta, ID

TaniFund | A financial technology company focusing on crowdfunding

- Promoted from Business Process Improvement specialist
- Initiated and supervised the Project Management team
- Created standardized process for loan application and approval
- Developed strategies for user retention and acquisition

Sourcing Encodage | October 2016 - August 2017 | Brussles, BE Bureau van Dijk - A Moody's Analytics

Key responsibilities: research and administration

Researcher | January 2014 - August 2015 | Jakarta, ID
Microfinance Innovation Center for Resources and Alternatives